As
the
storm clouds
gather
ominously
on the
distant
horizon
casting the
once
bright
sky into
the
muted
palette of
grey
and
violet the
air
took
an electric
charge
Thick
with the
promise
of
rain a
single
rumble
of thunder
echoed
across
the valley
stirring
birds
from their
perches
And
a moment
later
fat
Randolph began
to
fall
drumming softly
on
the
rooftop and
turning
dust
into slick
ribbons
while
people hurried
for
shelters
under awnings
and
the
atmosphere shifted
to
one
of calm
The
sounds
of raindrops
created
a
soothing backdrop
to
the
hustle of
those
seeking
refuge The
storm
seemed
to bring
a
strange
sense of
peace
amidst
the chaos
Outside
the
world transformed
as
puddles
formed and
the
scent
of wet
earth
filled
the air
This
was
the rhythmic
lullabies
of
Summer Downpours